tonetime.com 2007-05-21

# TONETIME

**TONETIME PRIVACY POLICY**

Your privacy is very important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information collection practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. **By visiting www.tonetime.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.** **You should check this Privacy Notice frequently to view updates and recent changes.**

 **The Information We Collect**

To improve the services we offer we log users' Internet Protocol Addresses (IP). An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your PC every time you browse the World Wide Web. Information for IP addresses is used for system administration to examine overall traffic trends, troubleshooting, etc. This information is used only in the aggregate form. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information, meaning the user session is tracked, but the user remains anonymous.

On certain pages of our website, you can subscribe to our services, order products, make requests, or register to receive materials. In these instances, we may ask you to provide your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number and credit card information (when subscribing to our service or ordering products only), as well as create a user name and password.

On some pages, you can submit information about other people, such as when you order a gift to be shipped to another person. In these instances, we may ask you to provide the recipient's name, mailing address, email address and telephone number.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to you PC's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to save you having to re-enter information such as your handset type.

The use of cookies is prevalent on the World Wide Web and many website use them. Although most web browsers accept cookies by default, the "Help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will direct you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies all together. Please be aware that cookies allow you to access some of the best features of our website, and we recommend that you leave them on.

**The Way TONETIME Uses Information**

In addition to processing your orders for the purchase of our services and products, we may use the information you provide to us for sending you special promotions and incentives, providing additional services, gathering demographic and website usage information, and improving our website and the quality of your online visits. We do not share personal information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your purchase orders. We use email addresses to answer the emails we receive and to send you your password if it is lost. We never disclose IP addresses to any third parties. Finally, we will not use your information in any manner unrelated to those described above. In the event we desire to make additional use of your information, we will provide you an opportunity to opt-out of such use.

 **Changing Your Profile and Opting-Out**

You can change your downloading profile at any time by logging into my locker with cell number and password. Once you have logged in, you can view your remaining credits or opt out of any subscribed services.

We recognize that you may not want to receive offers or other information from TONETIME. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving offers or other information from us by replying to the email or regular mail you receive from us and informing us of your request. You may also call customer service at **1-877-479-8230** to opt-out.
